https://www.outdoorsman.co.nz/page/privacy-statement

20-50% OFF STORE WIDE
HomeOnline ShopBikingBike AccessoriesBike ClothingBike GlovesBike HelmetsBike LightsBike Protection | Glasses | GogglesBike Tyres and PartsPark ToolsTyre Hand Pumps & InflatorsBooks | Maps | DVD'sMapsCamping, Hiking and TravelCamping AccessoriesPacks and Travel BagsTents and AccessoriesGazebo Sunwalls and AccessoriesTravel Adaptors and ProductsClothing and AccessoriesAccessoriesClothing Care ProductsMens ClothingWomen's ClothingChildrens ClothingElectronics/GPSGPSFishingBoat and Kayak AccessoriesFishing Books and DVD'sFishing Nets | Scales | GaffsFishing Rods, Reels, CombosFishing TackleSmokersWaders/Wading BootsFishing AccessoriesFly TyingFootwearCramponsGaiters/PuttiesKids FootwearMens FootwearWomen's FootwearShoe Care & AccessoriesHuntingGun SafesHunting AccessoriesOpticsSuppressorsFirearms PartsGun CasesKnives and SawsReloadingHydrationWatersportsLifejackets and FloatationPaddlesPool DonutsSwimwearWakeboards/Skates/SkisWeber BBQ AccessoriesShop By BrandAirfloAlveyBetacraftBirkenstockBlack MagicBobuxCatchColemanColumbiaCrocsDaiwaEMUElementalFoxGarminGasmateGearAidGiroGrangersHavasacHutchwilcoIcebreakerKilwellKiwi CampingLedlenserLekiLezyneLowaMarmotMerrellMons RoyaleMontaneNacsanOZtrailOkumaOluKaiOrvisPacsafePatagoniaRM WilliamsRailblazaSalomonScientific AnglersScottyShimano Fishing | CyclingSpeedoStoney CreekSwanndriTevaThe North FaceTimberlandUnder ArmourVigilanteVikingWaxenwolfWeberXTMZempireNews & SpecialsContact Us | FAQsDelivery | ReturnsPrivacy Statement
Privacy Statement
>Home >Contact Us | FAQs >Privacy Statement
Christmas ShippingIn order to allow plenty of time for busy couriers, the last day for orders to ensure they will get there in time for Christmas are:South Island: Sunday 13th DecemberNorth Island: Tuesday 15th December.
Privacy Statement:We collect personal information from you, including information about your:NameContact informationLocationBilling or purchase informationWe collect your personal information in order to:process internet orders order in special products for customerssend out newsletters and special offers for those who have signed up for them.Providing some information is optional.If you choose not to enter a form of contact, we'll be unable to advise you of a product arriving, or new specials and offers available online or in-store. If you would prefer not to receive our e-blasts, please use the unsubscibe button at the bottom of the email.You have the right to ask for a copy of any personal information we hold about you, and to ask for it to be corrected if you think it is wrong.If you’d like to ask for a copy of your information, or to have it corrected, please contact us at outdoorsmanhqnz@gmail.com
Top
DeliveryDelivery options and informationReturnsFind our returns and warranty information herePrivacy Policy
Visa, Mastercard, Internet Banking available.
Don't miss out!Subscribe to our newsletter for the latest updates.
© Copyright Outdoorsman HeadquartersOhope, New Zealand Website by Wild Paradise Enterprises
Menu Sitemap
Categories
